# Antonio Moreno



- - 0789201149
  - 6390, Engelberg
- Spanish ## 23/08/1988
  - github.com/4moreno

in

linkedin.com/in/amorenomtz

## **SKILLS**

- Tech Skills -

Ruby on Rails

HTML

CSS

Java Script

Boostrap

API

Figma UI/UX

- Soft Skills -

Team player

Solution oriented

Fast learner

Motivated

Responsible

LAN	uu	$\neg$	

Spanish

English

German

CERTIFICATES

JUNIOR FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

Fulltime coding bootcamp, working on real projects using Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS3, JavaScript & Github

### **PROFILE**

Recently graduated from @LeWagon Web development Bootcamp, where I've learned to work with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, GitHub, Figma and Bootstrap. I also developed with my team two projects using Ruby on Rails.

After 10 years as an early education and kindergarten teacher, I wanted to take my career to a new level and decided to seek a new challenge. I discovered in coding a new passion where can use my creative skills and solution-oriented abilities to create interesting and dynamic web applications.

#### **EDUCATION**

UX Design Certificate, Coursera - Google
09/2022 - present

Web Development Coding Bootcamp, Le Wagon - Online Batch 990
07/2022 - 09/2022

**Elementary School Teacher - Sports,** Almería University - Spain 09/2009 - 09/2012

Technician on Development of construction Projects,

Miguel de Cervantes University - Spain 09/2007 - 02/2009

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Kindergaden Teacher,** *Elementary School - Engelberg* 08/2020 - 07/2022

English teacher, Lil' Mouse House Bilingual Nursery - Rotkreuz
04/2018 - 07/2020

Recepcionist, Hotel Spannort, Engelberg 11/2017 - 03/2018

English teacher, KiddieLand Bilingual Nursery - Zürich
11/2016 - 10/2017

#### **PROJECTS**

travelmap.wiki, The Social Network for Travellers 🗷

https://rentall-yukilaurentiu.herokuapp.com/,
Renting platform, where users advertise and rent articles.